[

    {
        "question":"1) Which is the correct accessory? Status Relay Bundle - Provides 1 relay (3 total) for each of the following statuses, Normal Source Acceptability, Emergency Source Acceptability, Pre & Post Transfer Signal. Each relay has 2 NO/NC (Form C) sets of contacts rated for 6A at 120Vac, 250Vac Max.?",
        "choiceA":"31BG",
        "choiceB":"72EE2",
        "choiceC":"44G",
        "choiceD":"135L",
        "answer":"31BG"
    },
    {
        "question":"2) Which is the correct accessory? 5170 Quad-Ethernet Module provides transfer switch dashboard screen with password protected control capabilities, email alerts and open protocol support in a single module with an integrated 4 port Ethernet switch.",
        "choiceA":"99",
        "choiceB":"11BE",
        "choiceC":"72EE2",
        "choiceD":"12BS",
        "answer":"72EE2"
    },
    {
        "question":"3) Which is the correct accessory? Selective Load disconnect circuit to provide a pre-transfer and/or post transfer signal when transferring from emergency to normal and/or normal to emergency. The signal can be programmed to occur during all transfers or only when the transfer is occurring between two live sources. The length of the pre and post transfer delays can be set to 0-5 minutes 59 seconds.",
        "choiceA":"125A",
        "choiceB":"119M",
        "choiceC":"135L",
        "choiceD":"31Z",
        "answer":"31Z"
    },
    {
        "question":"4) Based off specs, which accessory is most appropriate? The switch shall be equipped with provisions to accept two-hole. long barrel, copper compression-type lugs.",
        "choiceA":"Accessory 62B1",
        "choiceB":"Accessory 63",
        "choiceC":"18RX",
        "choiceD":"Accessory 134",
        "answer":"Accessory 63"
    },
    {
        "question":"5) Based off specs, which accessory is most appropriate? Transfer Override Switch: Overrides automatic retransfer control so automatic transfer switch will remain connected to emergency power source regardless of condition of normal source. Pilot light indicates override status.",
        "choiceA":"6DL",
        "choiceB":"5L",
        "choiceC":"31CJ",
        "choiceD":"Accessory 1G",
        "answer":"6DL"
    },
    {
        "question":"6) Which of the following Accessories is standard on a 7000 series ATS?",
        "choiceA":"44G",
        "choiceB":"31Z",
        "choiceC":"11BE",
        "choiceD":"31BG",
        "answer":"11BE"
    },
    {
        "question":"7) Which of the following Accessories can be activated on a series 300 ATS?",
        "choiceA":"31Z",
        "choiceB":"72EE2",
        "choiceC":"11BE",
        "choiceD":"18RX",
        "answer":"31Z"
    },
    {
        "question":"8) Which of the following accessory combinations make up to be accessory 31BG?",
        "choiceA":"11BE, 7ES, 72EE2",
        "choiceB":"5L, 6DL, 11BE",
        "choiceC":"53BK, 14A, 29M",
        "choiceD":"11BE ,18RX, 31Z",
        "answer":"11BE ,18RX, 31Z"
    },
    {
        "question":"9) Which accessory is an equivelant to accessory 18RX for the 7000 series ATS?",
        "choiceA":"18RX2",
        "choiceB":"1G",
        "choiceC":"31BG",
        "choiceD":"31Z",
        "answer":"1G"
    },
    {
        "question":"10) Based off specs, which accessory is most appropriate? Load Test Switch: Load test switch to simulate normal power failure. (Maintained type).",
        "choiceA":"5L",
        "choiceB":"6DL",
        "choiceC":"31CJ",
        "choiceD":"11BE",
        "answer":"5L"
    },
    {
        "question":"11) True or False: Accessory 44G is standard on all NEMA 3R enclosures.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"False"
    },
    {
        "question":"12) True or False: H-Frame ATSs are available from 600A to 1200A",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    },
    {
        "question":"13) True or False: Seismic Qualification Data: Certificates, for transfer switches, accessories, and components, from manufacturer. Based off specs accessory 125A is being called out.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    },
    {
        "question":"14) True or False: ASCO Power Control Systems can be used to monitor and control the entire power distribution network of a facility, not just the ATS.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    },
    {
        "question":"15) True or False: The ASCO 300 Series ATS offers a 30-cycle closing and withstand rating.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    },
    {
        "question":"16) True or False: The ASCO 300G Generator Paralleling Control Switchgear allows for the seamless paralleling of multiple generators to meet varying load demands.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    },
    {
        "question":"17) True or False: ASCO's Load Bank Testing service is primarily used for the routine maintenance of generator sets and ATS units.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"False"
    },
    {
        "question":"18) True or False: ASCO ATSs with load shedding capabilities can automatically shed non-essential loads to ensure critical loads are adequately supplied with power during an outage.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    },
    {
        "question":"19) True or False: ASCO ATSs are designed for use with both DC (direct current) power systems, and AC (alternating current) power systems.",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"False"
    },
    {
        "question":"20) True or False: LED indicating lights shall be provided to indicated: bypass position, fully isolated position, and sourxe availiblty is standard on 7000 series ATSs",
        "choiceA":"True",
        "choiceB":"False",
        "answer":"True"
    }
    
]